HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005: A Finding Aid
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005
- Series II. Staff Photographs, 1940-2001
  - Subseries A. Staff, A-Z, circa 1940-circa 1994
    - Ann Monro, circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Karin B. Monsler (Research Assistant), 1993 (Box 36)
    - Jose Montealegre (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 36)
    - Juan Montermoso (Research Assistant), circa 1977 (Box 36)
    - George G. Montgomery, Jr. (Research Associate), circa 1959 (Box 36)
    - William Moonan (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Joseph R. Mooney (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Amanda Moore (Baker Library), circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - James F. Moore (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 36)
    - Russell Moore, circa 1961 (Box 36)
    - William E. Moran (Office of the Dean), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Leo A. Morehouse (Research Assistant), circa 1973 (Box 36)
    - Harvey Morgan (Research Assistant), circa 1966 (Box 36)
    - Ivor P. Morgan (Research Associate), circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Eliot F. Morrison (Research Assistant), circa 1964 (Box 36)
    - Richard James Morrison (Research Associate), circa 1961 (Box 36)
    - J. David Morrisy (Research Associate), circa 1968 (Box 36)
    - Louise B. Morse, 1960s (Box 36)
    - Michael S.S. Morton (Research Assistant), circa 1967 (Box 36)
    - George B. Mosely, circa 1965 (Box 36)
    - Susan Mosley, circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - Neil M. Moss (Research Assistant), circa 1968 (Box 36)
    - Mohamed Bacem Moussa (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 36)
    - Marian Mudarri (Division of Research), circa 1990 (Box 36)
    - Jeffrey M. Mudge (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Anne S. Mundo (Division of Computer Services), circa 1970 (Box 36)
    - Elizabeth H. Munro, circa 1980 (Box 36)
    - M. I. Murgatroyd, circa 1955 (Box 36)
    - Edwin A. Murray, Jr., circa 1971 (Box 36)
    - Ann D. Myers, 1970s (Box 36)
    - Eugene J. Nathan, circa 1960 (Box 37)
    - Thomas Neel (Executive Education), circa 1990 (Box 37)
    - Karen H. Nelson (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Howard H. Newman (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Ruth Newman, circa 1975 (Box 37)
    - Rand Neyland, circa 1975 (Box 37)
    - Jesse C. Nichols III (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 37)
    - Martha Nichols (Harvard Business Review), circa 1990 (Box 37)
    - Elizabeth Nill (MBA Program), circa 1984 (Box 37)
    - Patricial J. Nissen (Baker Library), circa 1975 (Box 37)
    - Jennifer N. Nixon (Case Services), 1992 (Box 37)
    - Richard L. Nohl, 1967 (Box 37)
    - William Nolan (Baker Library), circa 1990 (Box 37)
    - Newton Norman (Research Associate)d, circa 1975 (Box 37)
    - Jeri C. Norris (MBA Admissions), 1993 (Box 37)
    - David P. Norton (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Ruth Norton (Division of Research), 1960s (Box 37)
    - Vivian Nossiter (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 37)
    - Carl H. Novotny (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Pedro Nueno (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Augustine K. Nwabuzar (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Robert Paul O'Block (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - A. Marc O'Brien (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Elizabeth M. O'Brien, circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Vincent E. O'Brien (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - John O'Connor (Harvard Business Review), 1985 (Box 37)
    - Joseph J. O'Donnell (Executive Education), circa 1974 (Box 37)
    - Joseph P. O'Donnell (Trade Union Program), 1956-circa 1960 (Box 37)
    - Steve O'Donnell, 1987 (Box 37)
    - Dolores A. O'Hara (Baker Library), circa 1965 (Box 37)
    - Nancy O'Leary, 1985 (Box 37)
    - Eileen O'Malley, circa 1985 (Box 37)
    - Roberto V. Ongpin (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 37)
    - John A. Osborn, Jr. (HBS Press), 1994 (Box 37)
    - Mary E. Osgood, 1937 (Box 37)
    - Keri Ostrofsky, circa 1980 (Box 37)
    - Charles E. Ott (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 37)
    - James K. Owen (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Cheryl Ellen Owens, circa 1985 (Box 37)
    - Fabyan Packard (Health Services), 1938 (Box 37)
    - Chei-Min Pak (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Jonathan Palmer (Baker Library), circa 1980 (Box 37)
    - Joseph P.S. Pampel (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - George Pandapas (Division of Research), 1992 (Box 37)
    - Alix M. Paradis (HBS Fund), 1992 (Box 37)
    - Anne C. Parke, circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Deborah C. Parrott (HBS Press), 1993 (Box 37)
    - Donna Partridge (Harvard Business Review), 1979 (Box 37)
    - Micheal J. Passage, circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Mary-Ellen Patrell, circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Lawrence O. Paul, circa 1934 (Box 37)
    - Jon Paulson (Research Associate), circa 1975 (Box 37)
    - Robert J. Pavan (International Teachers Program), circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Vera Pawlowskis, 1980s (Box 37)
    - Richard B. Payne, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1985 (Box 37)
    - David A. Peach (Research Assistant), 1960s (Box 37)
    - Michael Pearce (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 37)
    - Nathan W. Pearson, 1934 (Box 37)
    - George S. Peer, circa 1954 (Box 37)
    - Roy Penchansky, circa 1965 (Box 37)
    - Peter Perkins, circa 1974 (Box 37)
    - Rita Perloff, 1986, (Contact sheets) (Box 37)
    - Nancy Perry (HBS Bulletin), 1990s (Box 37)
    - Carol Peterson, circa 1975 (Box 37)
    - Connie Peterson (Information Technology), 1993 (Box 37)
    - Larry Peterson (Doctoral Program), 1986 (Box 37)
    - Marvin W. Peterson (MBA Program), 1965 (Box 37)
    - Nancy Peterson, 1970s (Box 37)
    - Richard Phelps, circa 1980, (Contact sheets) (Box 37)
    - Vernon W. Pherson (Research Associate), circa 1957 (Box 37)
    - Etta Philbrook (Baker Library), 1939 (Box 37)
    - Sally Pian (Baker Library), 1990 (Box 37)
    - Laurent Augustin Picard (Research Associate), circa 1964 (Box 37)
    - Paul Pigors (Research Assistant), 1936 (Box 37)
    - Joan B. Pinck, circa 1972 (Box 37)
    - Robert A. Pitts (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 37)
    - Waddill Hunter Platt (Research Assistant), circa 1964 (Box 37)
    - Frank D. Plaut (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 37)
    - Hedwig Pocious, circa 1980 (Box 37)
    - Ruth Porritt, ca. 1950 (Box 37)
    - C. Robert Posthumus (Office of the Dean), circa 1965 (Box 37)
    - Faith A. Potter (Alumni Relations), circa 1965 (Box 37)
    - Diana Potts, circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Edward Prewitt, 1991 (Box 37)
    - Irene Profstein, circa 1975 (Box 37)
    - Edmond W. Pugh, Jr. (Office of the Dean), 1946 (Box 37)
    - Barbara Quill (MBA Admissions), 1978 (Box 37)
    - Robert D. Quinn, circa 1970 (Box 37)
    - Elizabeth L. Rachal (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 38)
    - Paul H. Rachal (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - David L. Rados (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Gary C. Raffaele (Trade Union Program), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Peter Rainey (Baker Library), 1991 (Box 38)
    - John A. Ratichek (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Talbot Rautoul, circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - William Rauwerdink (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Robert B. Ray (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Vincent R. Raymond (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Bonnie B. Reece (Research Associate), circa 1975 (Box 38)
    - Dorothea D. Reeves (Baker Library), 1950s (Box 38)
    - Marrilyn G. Reid, 1990s (Box 38)
    - Robert D. Reinhart, 1935 (Box 38)
    - Jo Ann Reufro (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - William Thomas Rhame (Research Assistant), circa 1938 (Box 38)
    - Lygeia Ricciardi (Research Assistant), circa 1985 (Box 38)
    - Frederick F. Richard, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Elizabeth Richardson (Research Associate), circa 1985 (Box 38)
    - Donald R. Riehl (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Richard C. Riggs, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - David C. Rikert (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Barbara Rimbach, 1970s (Box 38)
    - James G. Ripley (Harvard Business Review), circa 1969 (Box 38)
    - Donald B. Roberts (Office of Career Development), circa 1975 (Box 38)
    - James M. Roberts (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Marilynn A. Roberts, circa 1975 (Box 38)
    - Mervin H. Roberts, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Mike Roberts, circa 1980 (Box 38)
    - S. Jackie Prince Roberts (Research Associate), 1990s (Box 38)
    - Helen F. Rochlin (Business History Review), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - George Helm Rockwell, 1940s (Box 38)
    - Kenneth J. Rockwell (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Delmar J. Rogers (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Susan Rogers, 1980s (Box 38)
    - Susan A. Rogers (Research Assistant), circa 1968 (Box 38)
    - William H. Rogers (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Marilyn W. Roman, circa 1975 (Box 38)
    - Allan F. Rood, 1949-circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - Robert C. Ronstandt (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 38)
    - Louis Roquet (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 38)
    - Daniel Rosenberg (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - Paul Rosenberg (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - Sharon Rossi (Research Associate), 1992 (Box 38)
    - Nancy P. Rothbard (Research Associate), 1990-1991 (Box 38)
    - Lawrence Rothstein (Harvard Business Review), 1994 (Box 38)
    - Kalpana Row (Baker Library), 1994 (Box 38)
    - Edward D. Rowley, circa 1965-circa 1972 (Box 38)
    - I. Robert Rozen (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Ronald A. Rubel (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Andre Ruedi (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Richard P. Rumelt (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Carol Ruocco, 1981 (Box 38)
    - Christopher G. Russell (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - Gumars Rutkouskis (Baker Library), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Joseph Ryan (Division of Research), circa 1990 (Box 38)
    - James A. Saalfield (MBA Program), circa 1975 (Box 38)
    - Stanley E Sagov, Dr., (Health Services), circa 1980 (Box 38)
    - James E. Sailer (Research Associate), 1990 (Box 38)
    - Arnold R. Saitow (Research Associate), 1961 (Box 38)
    - Robert Q. Saldich (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - Lynn M. Salerno (Harvard Business Review), 1980s (Box 38)
    - Richard Salmon (Division of Research), circa 1990 (Box 38)
    - Stephen M. Salsbury (Research Associate), 1961 (Box 38)
    - Steven M. Salzinger (Research Associate), 1994 (Box 38)
    - Amanda Sandoval (MBA Program), 1992 (Box 38)
    - Michael Santoro, 1991 (Box 38)
    - Roy C. Satchell (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Jerome G. Saunders (Executive Education), circa 1990 (Box 38)
    - Brenda Schelling-Biggs (Division of Research), 1986 (Box 38)
    - Frederic M. Scherer (Research Associate), circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - Arthur A. Schoenwald (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - Samuel Schwartz (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Richard Schwem, circa 1985, (Contact sheet) (Box 38)
    - H. James Scott (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - David S. Searles, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Marian Search (Research Associate), circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - John Seeger (Research Associate), circa 1975 (Box 38)
    - Chester L. Seeley, circa 1938 (Box 38)
    - Andrew Segal (Research Associate), 1980s (Box 38)
    - Joanne Segal, Assistant Dean (External Relations), ca. 1986-1990s (Box 38)
    - Katherine Seger (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 38)
    - Joseph A. Seher (Research Associate), circa 1975 (Box 38)
    - J. McBrayer Sellers, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - Judith E. Selvidge (Research Assistant), circa 1972 (Box 38)
    - Sterling D. Sessions (Research Assistant), circa 1962 (Box 38)
    - Charles O. Sethness (External Relations), circa 1966-1990s (Box 38)
    - Nancy Seymour, circa 1965 (Box 38)
    - Sally Seymour, circa 1980 (Box 38)
    - John A. Shane, circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - Barbara Shank (Division of Research), circa 1985 (Box 38)
    - David Shavit (Baker Library), circa 1960 (Box 38)
    - Hillary Shaw, circa 1985 (Box 38)
    - William D. Shea (MBA Program), circa 1980 (Box 38)
    - Peter R. Sherer, 1972 (Box 38)
    - Marilyn Shesko, 1980s (Box 38)
    - Sunglim Allison Shin (MBA Counseling Service), 1990s (Box 38)
    - Michael Shinnar (Research Assistant), circa 1963 (Box 38)
    - Janet G. Short (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Kenneth Simmonds (Research Assistant), circa 1963 (Box 38)
    - Jerrold G. Simon (MBA Counseling Service), circa 1970 (Box 38)
    - Janet Simpson (MBA Program), circa 1995 (Box 38)
    - Kenneth L. Simpson, 1935 (Box 38)
    - Kuljot Singh (Research Associate), circa 1994 (Box 38)
    - Nancy Sinsabaugh, circa 1990 (Box 38)
    - Harvey N. Singer (Research Assistant), circa 1972 (Box 39)
    - Andrew J. Silver (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 39)
    - Mathew R. Simmons (Research Associate), circa 1967 (Box 39)
    - Gerald A. Simon (Research Assistant), circa 1956 (Box 39)
    - Saumitra Sircar (Research Associate), circa 1976 (Box 39)
    - Peter J. Siris (Research Assistant), circa 1968 (Box 39)
    - Allan P. Slaff, circa 1973 (Box 39)
    - Carl B. Slenk (Research Assistant), 1961 (Box 39)
    - Norton Q. Sloan (Research Assistant), circa 1961 (Box 39)
    - Arthur A. Sloane (Research Assistant), circa 1963 (Box 39)
    - Gregory S. Smirin (Executive Education), 1991 (Box 39)
    - Geoffrey W. Smith (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 39)
    - Homer O. Smith, Director (MBA Program), circa 1973 (Box 39)
    - John B. Smith, Jr., circa 1991 (Box 39)
    - Kenneth G. Smith (MBA Admissions), 1991-1992 (Box 39)
    - O. Guinn Smith, 1961 (Box 39)
    - Stephen K. Smith (Research Associate), 1985 (Box 39)
    - Wendy Smith (Research Associate), 1980s (Box 39)
    - Lee Ann Snedeker, (HBS Press), 1993 (Box 39)
    - Donald R. Sohn (Research Associate), circa 1951 (Box 39)
    - Susan M. Southworth (Baker Library), 1970s (Box 39)
    - Anna E. Spang (Baker Library), 1969 (Box 39)
    - Norman W. Spaulding, III (Research Assistant), 1993 (Box 39)
    - Cummins E. Speakman, Jr., 1960s (Box 39)
    - Harold S. Spear (Research Associate), circa 1958 (Box 39)
    - Padraic "Paddy" Spence (Research Associate), circa 1992 (Box 39)
    - Shirley Spence (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 39)
    - Leslie L. Spero (Research Assistant), circa 1980 (Box 39)
    - Beverly Splane, 1973 (Box 39)
    - Q. M. Spooner, circa 1960 (Box 39)
    - Linda G. Sprague (Research Assistant), circa 1973 (Box 39)
    - Audrey T. Sproat (Research Associate), circa 1960 (Box 39)
    - Enid Star (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 39)
    - Laurence E. Steadman (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 39)
    - Melvin J. Steckler (Research Associate), circa 1967 (Box 39)
    - John E. Steele, 1960s (Box 39)
    - Sally Steinberg (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 39)
    - Michael Stevenson (Baker Library), circa 1990 (Box 39)
    - Edward S. Stimpson (Research Assistant), circa 1958 (Box 39)
    - Sam B. Stocking, 1939 (Box 39)
    - Patricia A. Stockton (Baker Library), circa 1970 (Box 39)
    - John M. Stopford (Research Associate), circa 1968 (Box 39)
    - Christine Stranberg, 1993 (Box 39)
    - Tina Strauss, 1991-1992 (Box 39)
    - Robert A. Strickland, 1992 (Box 39)
    - Robert A. Stringer (Research Assistant), circa 1966 (Box 39)
    - Alexander D. Stuart, circa 1975 (Box 39)
    - Carolyn Stubbs (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 39)
    - Cheryl R. Suchors, circa 1970 (Box 39)
    - Amy G. Sugerman, circa 1990 (Box 39)
    - William A. Sugg, circa 1937 (Box 39)
    - Josephine Anne Sullivan, 1980s (Box 39)
    - Laurie A. Sullivan, 1993 (Box 39)
    - Robert E. Surtees (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 39)
    - Cedric L. Suzman (Research Assistant), circa 1964 (Box 39)
    - Robert E. Svensk (Research Assistant), circa 1972 (Box 39)
    - Andrew Swan (Baker Library), 1992 (Box 39)
    - Floyd T. Swann (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 39)
    - Gordon S. Schwartz (Research Associate), 1980s (Box 39)
    - Stephen B. Swensrud (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 39)
    - Stephen L. Sykes (Harvard Business Review), circa 1990 (Box 39)
    - Williston B. Symonds (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 39)
    - Suzanne Mosley Synnott (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 39)
    - Sarah A.L. Tabler (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 39)
    - Elizabeth Talerman (Executive Education), 1994 (Box 39)
    - Gregory Tanaka (MBA Admissions), circa 1990 (Box 39)
    - Diane Taylor (Alumni Relations), circa 1992 (Box 39)
    - Marilyn L. Taylor (Research Associate), circa 1974 (Box 39)
    - Thomas Teal (Harvard Business Review), circa 1990 (Box 39)
    - Ann B. Teixeira (Executive Education), circa 1980 (Box 39)
    - Bridget Testa (Executive Education), 1990s (Box 39)
    - Sarah Thayer (HBS Fund), circa 1990 (Box 39)
    - Donald R Theophilus, Jr., 1967 (Box 39)
    - Paul T. Tierney, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1968 (Box 39)
    - Mark A. Tillinghast (Research Associate), circa 1994 (Box 39)
    - Ralph B. Titus (Harvard Business Review), circa 1985 (Box 39)
    - Bernard F. Tobin (Visiting Consultant), 1960 (Box 40)
    - Freddi Tompkins, 1980s (Box 40)
    - Breffni Tomlin (Research Associate), 1973 (Box 40)
    - Joseph F. Toot (Research Assistant), circa 1961 (Box 40)
    - Endre Toth (Research Assistant), 1971 (Box 40)
    - Phillip Townsend (Research Associate), 1973 (Box 40)
    - Norman E. Toy (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 40)
    - Robert Traupe (Research Assistant), 1973 (Box 40)
    - James F. Trees (Research Associate), circa 1963 (Box 40)
    - Karin E. Trelease (Doctoral Program), circa 1965 (Box 40)
    - Nancy H. Treverton (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 40)
    - Steven K. Troofott (Research Assistant), circa 1965 (Box 40)
    - Elizabeth F. Trotman (Research Associate), circa 1965 (Box 40)
    - H. Anton Tucher (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 40)
    - Wilbur H. Turk (Baker Library), 1980s (Box 40)
    - Robert B. Ullian (Health Services), circa 1971 (Box 40)
    - Julio Urgel (Research Associate), circa 1991 (Box 40)
    - Jerry V. Useem (Research Assistant), circa 1994 (Box 40)
    - Eduardo Vallarino, Jr. (INCAE), circa 1965 (Box 40)
    - Zbynek L. Vancura (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 40)
    - Hans M.M. van der Ven, circa 1990 (Box 40)
    - Harold P. Van Gorder (Advanced Management Program), circa 1963 (Box 40)
    - James Van Vleck (Research Assistant), circa 1956 (Box 40)
    - Vicki E. Gugyeras Vanderbark (Research Assistant), circa 1975 (Box 40)
    - Gonzalo Verdugo (Research Assistant), circa 1974 (Box 40)
    - Gertrude Verser (Research Associate), circa 1978 (Box 40)
    - Karl H. Vesper (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 40)
    - Susan G. Vishner, circa 1985 (Box 40)
    - Stuart J. Vidockler (Research Assistant), circa 1968 (Box 40)
    - Rebecca W. Voorheis (Research Assistant), 1993 (Box 40)
    - Barbara F. Voss, circa 1970 (Box 40)
    - Eliot Wadsworth, II (Research Assistant), circa 1968 (Box 40)
    - Gerald C. Wagner (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 40)
    - Richard Wailes, circa 1977 (Box 40)
    - Charles P. Waite (Research Assistant), circa 1959 (Box 40)
    - Athur H. Walker (Research Assistant), circa 1957 (Box 40)
    - Donald Wallace (Research Associate), 1973 (Box 40)
    - Ennis J. Walton (Research Assistant), circa 1990 (Box 40)
    - Marion M. Walton, Jr. (Research Assistant), circa 1967 (Box 40)
    - Ranne Warner (Research Associate), 1974 (Box 40)
    - Alison H. Watson (Research Associate), 1992 (Box 40)
    - William S. Warren, Jr. (Office of the Dean), circa 1957 (Box 40)
    - Donald J. Watson (The Executive), circa 1965 (Box 40)
    - James G. Wayne (Research Assistant), 1970 (Box 40)
    - Kenneth P. Wayne (Research Assistant), circa 1974 (Box 40)
    - Gwendolyn Weaver (Baker Library), circa 1980 (Box 40)
    - Allen Webb (Research Associate), 1992 (Box 40)
    - Alan M. Webber (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 40)
    - James B. Weber (Research Associate), 1994 (Box 40)
    - Nancy T. Weber (Research Assistant), circa 1990 (Box 40)
    - Rohan S. Weerasinghe (Research Assistant), circa 1974 (Box 40)
    - James A. Wegge (Research Assistant), 1971 (Box 40)
    - Charles B. Weigle (Research Assistant), 1971 (Box 40)
    - Roberta F. Weinshenker, 1992 (Box 40)
    - Abbott D. Weiss (Research Assistant), circa 1970 (Box 40)
    - Gary E. Welch (Research Assistant), circa 1968 (Box 40)
    - Sharon S. Wendell (Department of Operations), 1993 (Box 40)
    - Thomas W. Wenstrand (Research Assistant), 1972 (Box 40)
    - David R. Wesley (MBA Placement), 1993 (Box 40)
    - Jill Westfall (MBA Program), 1990s (Box 40)
    - Kirby B. Westheimer (Research Associate), circa 1961 (Box 40)
    - Emily Wheeler (HBS Publishing), 1993 (Box 40)
    - Mary E. Whelan, circa 1975 (Box 40)
    - Margaret D. White, circa 1980 (Box 40)
    - Mary T. White, circa 1945-1971 (Box 40)
    - Ann Whitehead, circa 1990 (Box 40)
    - Steven Whitelaw (Research Assistant), 1972 (Box 40)
    - Frederick M. Whitmeyer (Research Associate), circa 1975 (Box 40)
    - Robert B. Whittemore, 1970s (Box 40)
    - Sarah B. Wicks (Office of Career Development), circa 1970 (Box 40)
    - John Wilding (Research Associate), circa 1967 (Box 40)
    - Bernaree P. Wiley (Research Assistant), 1972 (Box 40)
    - Warren Wilhelm, circa 1974 (Box 40)
    - Willis H .Willey (Research Assistant), circa 1967 (Box 40)
    - Harriette G. Williams (Baker Library), circa 1959 (Box 40)
    - John S. Williams (Research Assistant), 1973 (Box 40)
    - Nancy F. Williams, 1970s (Box 40)
    - Alistair F. Williamson (HBS Press), 1993 (Box 40)
    - Vincent N. Willis (Research Associate), circa 1992 (Box 40)
    - Geraldine Willigan (Harvard Business Review), circa 1990 (Box 40)
    - Brent D. Wilson (Research Assistant), circa 1979 (Box 40)
    - Michele Wilson, circa 1985 (Box 40)
    - George A. Wiltsee, 1970s (Box 40)
    - Oliver Wing, circa 1947 (Box 40)
    - Dietmar Winkler (Harvard Business Review), circa 1975 (Box 40)
    - Priscilla Winslow, circa 1965 (Box 40)
    - Bessie Wisotel, 1979 (Box 40)
    - A. Wohl (Executive Education), circa 1973 (Box 40)
    - Francis W. Wolek (Research Associate), circa 1970 (Box 40)
    - Robert A. Wolf (Research Assistant), circa 1959 (Box 40)
    - Paige Woltzen, circa 1990, (Contact sheets) (Box 40)
    - Audris S. Wong (Research Associate), 1989 (Box 40)
    - S. Francis Woods (Baker Library), 1970 (Box 40)
    - Debra A. Woog (Research Associate), circa 1994 (Box 40)
    - William Work, circa 1990 (Box 40)
    - Lawrence H. Wortzel (Research Associate), circa 1960 (Box 40)
    - Courtenay P. Worthington, Jr. (Research Associate), circa 1959 (Box 40)
    - Linda C. Woycik (Research Assistant), 1972 (Box 40)
    - Donald M. Wright (Alumni Relations), 1950s-1960s (Box 40)
    - John M. Wynne, Jr. (Research Associate), 1971 (Box 40)
    - Pamela A. Yatsko (Research Associate), 1993 (Box 41)
    - Wendell A Yeatts (Baker Library), circa 1965 (Box 41)
    - Patricia Yee (MBA Program), 1972 (Box 41)
    - Shim Kim Yoo (Research Associate), circa 1990 (Box 41)
    - S. William Yost (Research Associate), circa 1969 (Box 41)
    - Allegra J. Young (Research Associate), 1992 (Box 41)
    - Raymond A. Young, III (Research Assistant), 1971 (Box 41)
    - Susan Young circa 1994 (Box 41)
    - Norman Zachary, Dr. (Computing Center), 1966 (Box 41)
    - Charles R. Zaitman (Research Assistant), circa 1960 (Box 41)
    - Samuel S. Zanghi (Audio-Visual Education), 1956-circa 1970 (Box 41)